insuranceleadz.com 2007-12-17

# InsuranceLeadz - Privacy Policy

## What information do we collect?

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. When you request a quote or purchase financial services on this site we ask for your personally identifiable information such as your name, phone number, address, e-mail address and social security number. 
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive this information from your computer when you visit our Web site, including the Web site you visited before ours, your browser, screen resolution, and operating system. We also store "cookies" on your computer to save information entered during the quoting and comparative rate process, and collect technical data, such as your Internet protocol (IP) address, operating system, and session ID. 
  * **Information from Other Sources:** We will receive information from those referring you to us. We will keep and update information necessary to provide comparative quotes and to service financial services. We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. 

## How do we use this information?

All information you give us on this Web site is stored on our computer servers.

Our business changes constantly. This Privacy policy will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We invite customers to visit the website occasionally to check for program changes and the latest Privacy Statement. Please note that this Privacy Policy only governs the data held by InsuranceLeadz.com and does not apply to the participating financial service provider once you purchase their services. We encourage you to read their policies.

## Links to other Web Sites

During your visit to our site, you may come across links that will take you to third-party Web sites. InsuranceLeadz.com does not control the content of or the information collected from these third-party Web sites. These third-party Web sites are not subject to InsuranceLister.com's Privacy Policy. Links to third-party sites do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement, or approval by InsuranceLeadz.com of the content, policies, or practices of such sites. Therefore, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of these sites before you disclose your personal information to these other parties.

## Children

InsuranceLeadz.com does not sell products for purchase by children nor is this site intended for use by children. InsuranceLeadz.com abides by the Children's On-Line Privacy Protection Act.

## Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit InsuranceLeadz.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Ohio. If you have any concern about privacy at InsuranceLeadz.com, please send us a thorough description to: webmaster (AT) insuranceleadz.com and we will try to resolve it. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.

## Glossary

**Cookie:** A small text file of information saved in the browser when you access certain Web pages. Cookies hold information that identifies you to the Web site (and only that Web site) that gave you the cookie.

**Internet protocol (IP) address** : The numbers that are translated into a domain name (e.g., InsuranceLister.com). The address is a string of four numbers separated by periods (such as 111.22.3.244) used to represent a computer or other device on the Internet.

**Operating system:** The program responsible for overseeing the basic hardware resources of a computer such as disk drives, memory, keyboard, screen, and CPU. UNIX, DOS, Windows, and Macintosh System 7 are examples of operating systems.

**Session ID:** The code used to keep track of a person (using a browser) as he or she interacts with a server. Since the server may interact with many people simultaneously, a session ID is needed to keep track of each person individually.

**Your privacy is important to us.**  
At InsuranceLeadz.com, we use the highest level of security available to safeguard your personal information. We hate spam just as much as you do, so we'll never sell or rent your email address for mass marketing.
